[Music]
once upon a time on the shore of the
deep blue sea
a fisherman and his wife were living in
a tiny cottage
the fisherman used to go to the seaside
every day and fish with his fishing rod
he was quite content to live like this
but his wife was not as happy as he was
ugh look at that disgusting cottage
moldy and damp everywhere i am tired of
cleaning every day
the fisherman was very much in love with
his wife but no matter what he did he
could not make her happy
if he brings her fish she wants crab if
he picks apples she craves pears
one day the fisherman went fishing as
usual he swung his fishing rod into the
water and started to wait
after a few hours the tip of his fishing
rod finally trembled
oh a fish hit the hook but
ouch
this must be a stubborn big fish
the fisherman pulled pulled pulled and
was surprised to finally see the
flounder on the tip of his fishing rod
because this fish was golden and shining
brightly
you finally managed to catch me didn't
you fisherman
huh
did you just talk to me or am i going
crazy
you heard right fisherman but listen
i'm not like the other fishes i'm
actually a prince under a spell
i can't believe this
free me fishermen please don't kill me
even
make a wish and i'll make it come true
because you saved me
no no
no need i've never seen a talking fish
before
of course i will free you come on go
back to the seas
the fisherman returned home with great
excitement
why did you come back early didn't you
catch fish couldn't you at least bring
some fruit
no darling i caught a fish today but
but
but that fish was talking he told me he
was actually a prince
what and what happened then
well then he asked me to make a wish
but that moment i was shocked and i
immediately let him back into the water
so you found a magic fish and left it
back in the water without asking for
anything huh i cannot believe you you
saved his life you could make a wish in
return like a house
go catch that fish again and ask for a
new home to make me happy
the fisherman could not refuse his
wife's request and went back to the
seaside
[Music]
flounder flounder fish prince i just
wanna make a wish come on make through
this wish tick tock tick tock
the fish just came out of the water
what do you want fisherman tell me
my wife is not happy at all
tired of living in a cottage she wants a
nice house
so go home fisherman she has a new home
now
[Music]
the fisherman ran home and saw his wife
standing in front of a perfect house
the inside of the house was full of
brand new furniture and everywhere was
immaculate
oh husband we will no longer live in a
cottage but in a wonderful house and
everything is new and clean
yes my wife now we can live happily ever
after in this house right
[Music]
that night the fisherman's wife could
not sleep
[Music]
as soon as the morning came
she made another request from her
husband at the breakfast table
husband this house seems too small for
us
i want a bigger house
even a palace
what
i want to be a queen don't you
understand
go and tell that to the fish prince
the fisherman went to the seaside with
thoughts in his head
flounder flounder fish prince i just
wanna make a wish come on make through
this wish tick tock tick tock
my wife is not happy at all
why fisherman
she wants to have a palace
so go home fishermen your wife now lives
in a palace
when the fisherman returned he saw that
there was now a huge palace where his
house was
and his wife was sitting on a huge
throne in the palace hall
my darling you really have become a
queen
[Music]
yes
so are you happy now
no
i actually want to be the empress not
the
queen what a fish can't make you an
empress do you understand
let the fish prince decide that come on
move go ask the fish to make me the
empress
the poor fisherman went to the seaside
sadly to make his wife happy
flounder flounder fish prince i just
wanna make a wish come on make through
this wish tick tock tick tock
my wife is still not happy
well is that so
so what does she want this time
she
she wants to be an empress
so go home fisherman your wife is now an
when the fisherman came running back he
could not believe his eyes the palace
was now much larger than before moreover
there were guards at the door
his wife on the other hand was now
sitting on a more glorious throne as an
empress
oh my darling you really have become an
so are you happy now
hmm
i don't know we'll talk about it later
i'm so tired today we better sleep now
the fisherman and his wife lay on the
bed to sleep
the fisherman fell asleep praying that
his wife would not want anything more
from him
she had been thinking all night about
what more she could want from that magic
fish
week has passed
the woman called her husband before her
and made a request
husband
time keeps running out
i want to control time
i want to live above the clouds and rule
the sun and the moon
what are you saying wife
why do you want such a thing why is this
abundance wealth and power not enough
if you want me to be happy go to that
fish prince now and tell him my wish
i can't do this my darling please stop
now
oh
but
don't you want me to be happy the
fisherman risked everything to make his
wife happy
and went to the seaside again
flounder flounder fish prince i just
wanna make a wish come on make to this
my wife is still not happy
i'm sorry about that fisherman what does
she want this time
my wife wants to control time she wants
to rule the sun and the moon in a palace
above the clouds
alright fisherman go home
when the fisherman came running back
neither his wife nor the palace were
there
when he looked up he saw that the clouds
were far away from
him my wife where are you you are far
from me now
the fishermen hurried back to the
seashore and called the fish prince
flounder flounder fish prince i just
want to make a wish come on make through
this wish tick tock tick tock
what happened to my wife
i just fulfilled her wish she gave up
everything to rule time above the clouds
so neither you can see her nor can she
see you
oh fish prince i saved your life but i
never asked you for a wish myself i
always wanted something for my wife
please help me give me back my wife
hmm you're right fisherman
tell me what is your wish
may my wife always be with me and very
happy this is my wish well fisherman go
home your wife has everything to be
the fisherman ran home with great
excitement he was very surprised to see
this new situation
his wife was waiting for him in front of
the cottage just like in the old days
oh my husband
i couldn't realize the worth of what i
had i was actually very happy with you
in this small and cute cottage
from that day on the fisherman's wife
understood that even the smallest things
thus they lived happily ever after in a
clean house with delicious food every
day
[Music]