Hi, I am Professor Mo's tour and I will
be telling you about water. You can call
it rain, you can call it snow, you can
call it sleep, you can call it hail, but
it's water all the same. Did you ever
wonder how old water is or where it
comes from? The answers may surprise
you. The next time you see a pond or
even a glass of water, think about how
old that water might be. Do you really
want to know? I thought you did. Did you
brush your teeth this morning? Well,
some of the water that you used could
have fallen from the sky yesterday or a
week or a month ago. It's pretty new.
But some part of that water is very old
and was around during the time of the
dinosaurs or even longer. Or maybe it's
a little newer like from the time when
the pharaohs were building
pyramids. You see there is only a
limited amount of water and it gets
recycled. Yeah. It keeps going round and
round that we call it the water cycle.
Yes. You have a question. No, it's not
like a jet ski or a bicycle for water.
It is nothing you can ride. It is how
water keeps going round and round. Let
me
explain. First, I would like to say that
water is very
important. Imagine an empty lake. The
fish would be very
unhappy. Imagine an empty ocean. Your
day at the beach would be like going to
a desert. And since you are mostly made
up of water, let's just say you would be
a lot lighter. The water cycle has four
parts. Evaporation, condensation,
precipitation,
collection. Evaporation. When the water
in an ocean, a lake, a pond, a river, or
a stream is heated by the sun, it turns
into vapor or steam. It then floats into
the air. Of course, when you are out on
a hot day or you exercise, you sweat.
Well, guess what? That evaporates, too.
What about those drops of dew on leaves
or the grass? Yes, they too evaporate
and become a part of the water
cycle. Condensation. As the water vapor
gets cooled, it changes back into a
liquid and turns into
clouds. Precipitation. When the air in
the clouds cannot hold any more liquid,
it falls back to the ground. It returns
in different ways depending on the
temperature and where it comes down. It
can fall as rain or it can fall as snow.
Did you know that no two
snowflakes are the same? It can return
as sleet, which is like rain that has
almost frozen, or it can come as hail.
Those frozen balls of rain that can
actually break windows and dent cars.
Collection, no matter how it comes down,
it is collected and stored. It can fall
into the ocean, lake, pond, river, or
stream. If it lands on the ground, it
may roll into a river or be sucked up by
the soil. It may even pass through the
ground to an underground lake or river
to be used later. Now, what happens
tomorrow when the sun comes out? That's
right. The water cycle starts over
again. Oops, the sun is out. But don't
worry, Professor Ma's tour will return
after all. I am a part of the water
cycle.